MANOJ KUMAR N (1) Featured

Full stack developer with 15+ experience seeking role as Technical Architect, Software Development, Perl, PHP, Python, Javascript, Node.js, jQuery, MySQL, ORACLE, Apache, Hybrid Mobile Apps, Chatbots



Current Designation: Principal Software Developer Total Experience: 15 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Oracle India Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Germany, Singapore Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Perl, PHP, MySQL, Javascript, Node.Js, Python, ¡Query, Html5, Apache, MySql, Oracle, Hybrid Mobile Apps,

Chatbots, Cloud Technologies

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Summary

15+ years of experience in Full Stack development (LAMP) with specialization in Perl, PHP, Python, MySQL/Oracle, Apache and Linux.

Experience in JavaScript Hybrid Mobile development technologies like Cordova and Oracle JET Experience in Node.js, JavaScript frameworks such as jQuery and Web Services like REST, SOAP Experience working in Oracle technologies like OMH, ODA & VBCS

Work Experience

Oracle India as Principal Software Developer May 2011 to Till Date

Responsible for Design & Development of Software products and tools

Mahindra Satyam as Sr. Software Engineer May 2008 to Apr 2011

Ed Ventures E-learning Pvt Ltd as Software Engineer Jul 2005 to May 2008

Design and development of software tools and web applications

Education

UG: B.A (MATHEMATICS, STATISTICS AND ECONOMICS) from S.V University, Tirupati in 2001

PG: MCA (Computers) from S.V University, Tirupati in 2004

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Linux, Apple MAC, Win 7			
Perl, JavaScript, PHP, Python, Java			
Oracle 11i, MySQL 5, Postgres SQL			
JavaScript, JQuery			0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
HTML5, CSS3			
OMH, ODA, Oracle JET			
Apache 2 with mod_perl and mod_php			
CVS, Perforce, SVN, Git			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
Hindi				
English				
Telugu				
Kannada				

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time